<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<!-- Generated using X-Studio -->
<language id="44">

	<page id="8102" title="PwnMi" desc="" voice="no">
		<t id="1">\33GPwn\33BMi\33X v0.5.1</t>
		<t id="2">By Zanzal - LICENSE: CC-BY-SA 4.0 International - http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/legalcode\n</t>
		<t id="3">PwnMi</t>
		<t id="4">{17,5883} {13,24}</t>
		<t id="5">{1337,3} uninstalled.</t>
		<t id="6">\\\\Public Wireless Network for Meta Interaction&gt;</t>
		<t id="7">\33Gnone\33X</t>
		<t id="8">\33Bvery little\33X</t>
		<t id="9">\33Ymoderate\33X</t>
		<t id="10">\33Ointense\33X</t>
		<t id="11">\33Rextreme\33X</t>
		<t id="12">\33Mpermaban\33X</t>
		<t id="13">They are completely oblivious to your actions.</t>
		<t id="14">Your activities may have been noticed but as for now you`ve managed to cover all traces of the origin.</t>
		<t id="15">They recently upgraded their security system for no apparent reason, but that hasn`t stopped you.</t>
		<t id="16">There is some evidence that they have hired an outside consultant to review their systems.</t>
		<t id="17">They are on to you, but they haven`t quite figured out the extent of your activities nor have they figured out how to shut you down.</t>
		<t id="18">\33R**** Access Denied ****\33X</t>
		<t id="19">Exit</t>
		<t id="20">Station Privilege Level: \33W%s\33X\nStation Suspicion Rating: %s\n\nHacker Grade: %s</t>
		<t id="21">\33MA\053\33X</t>
		<t id="22">\33RA\33X</t>
		<t id="23">\33GB\33X</t>
		<t id="24">\33YC\33X\n</t>
		<t id="25">Status Report</t>
		<t id="26">Guest Level Commands</t>
		<t id="27">Proxy Access</t>
		<t id="28">Remote Execution</t>
		<t id="29">Private Key Access</t>
		<t id="30">Root Access</t>
		<t id="31">Command and Control</t>
		<t id="32">You are not experienced enough to hack a facility with this level of security.</t>
		<t id="33">Stations in hacking range</t>
		<t id="34">Suspicion</t>
		<t id="35">Back</t>
		<t id="36">Stations In Range</t>
		<t id="37">Targeted Station</t>
		<t id="38">PLvl</t>
		<t id="39">\33W%s\33X</t>
		<t id="40">\33B%s\33W\n\n%s\n\n\33YRisk Assessment:\33W\nRisk = \33R%s\33W\nReward = \33G%s\33X</t>
		<t id="41">Conduct Port Scan</t>
		<t id="42">Attempt to identify unsecured ports for use in future hacks.</t>
		<t id="43">Social Engineering: Unsuspecting victim</t>
		<t id="44">Put an ad in on the local social network, make a friend, and use this friend to attempt to gain an advantage within the station network. If you are clever enough not to raise to many flags then you shouldn`t raise too much suspicion but the gains may not be that impressive.</t>
		<t id="45">Social Engineering: The Insider</t>
		<t id="46">\33YHire\33X an accomplice to get you more access. If your accomplice gets caught you risk a permaban.</t>
		<t id="47">Cross Site Scripting</t>
		<t id="48">Embed malicious script code in a BBS forum. Automated security systems will quickly detect this attack and it will raise some suspicion; however, it will also increase your privilege rating with one random station within comms range of the targeted station.</t>
		<t id="49">\33GSuccess!\33X</t>
		<t id="50">\33YPartial Success.\33X</t>
		<t id="51">\33RFailure!\33X</t>
		<t id="52">little</t>
		<t id="53">some</t>
		<t id="54">moderate</t>
		<t id="55">high</t>
		<t id="56">extreme</t>
		<t id="57">Begin Hacking Op</t>
		<t id="58">This is going to cost you \33Y%scr\33X. Do we have a deal?</t>
		<t id="59">Resource cost is %scr. Proceed?</t>
		<t id="60">Proceed</t>
		<t id="61">Cancel</t>
		<t id="62">Social Engineering...\(\33Y%s\33X%%\)</t>
		<t id="63">Hacking...\(\33Y%s\33X%%\)</t>
		<t id="64">Scanning...\(\33Y%s\33X%%\)</t>
		<t id="65">\nYour hacking skills have increased a grade.\n\n\n</t>
		<t id="66">Station: %s - %s\nNew PLvl = %s, Suspicion = %s\n\n</t>
		<t id="67">History</t>
		<t id="68">\33WResults of \33Y%s\33W against \33B%s\33W:\n\n\33X</t>
		<t id="69">Map Internal Network</t>
		<t id="70">Browse Blogs</t>
		<t id="71">Remote Dictionary Attack</t>
		<t id="72">Remote Port Scan</t>
		<t id="73">Using a misconfigured FTP server you can attempt to map out their internal network. This will affect all stations in range of the targetted station.</t>
		<t id="74">Access the stations internal public website to browse station employees blogs for clues that might help you gain access to a station within range.</t>
		<t id="75">Relay a dictionary attack through the target stations proxy server. Suspicion gained will be applied to the station you use to proxy your attack.</t>
		<t id="76">Instead of conducting a port scan from your ship, you can use the station proxy to do the work for you. Only works if proxy target has not been port scanned already.</t>
		<t id="77">Researching...\(\33Y%s\33X%%\)</t>
		<t id="78">Tier</t>
		<t id="79">Hacker Status</t>
		<t id="80">Known Stations</t>
		<t id="81">\33YSuspicion Redirected\33X</t>
		<t id="82">Which station will you target?</t>
		<t id="83">Next Grade</t>
		<t id="84">Hacking Grade</t>
		<t id="85">Decrypt Passwords File</t>
		<t id="86">Alter Log Files</t>
		<t id="87">Create Fake Identity</t>
		<t id="88">Social Engineering: Helpdesk Technician</t>
		<t id="89">Attempt to decrypt passwords in a file stored on the remote server.</t>
		<t id="90">Alter the log files in an attempt to disguise your hacking against the target station. If the command succeeds it reduces suspicion by a percentage. The more they suspect you the more effective this command is.</t>
		<t id="91">Using access to various internal systems you attempt to create a fake identity for future attacks. Each time you use the fake identity you will be at risk of having it exposed.</t>
		<t id="92">Using your fake identity and information gathered from previous attacks try and get a help desk technician to reset a users password for you.</t>
		<t id="93">\(id needed\)</t>
		<t id="94">Plant Trojan</t>
		<t id="95">Social Engineering: Bad URL</t>
		<t id="96">Distribute Patch</t>
		<t id="97">Using one of the code signing certificates you have access to, sign a blatantly malicious program and leave it where someone accessing the station`s server might find it. This will generate some suspicion, but it could also give you the boost you need to gain root access.</t>
		<t id="98">Monitor social sites to see if someone requests a download link for a software package that you have code signing access for. This will allow you to upload a malicious payload affecting random users within range of this station.</t>
		<t id="99">Using your fake identity as a station software developer intentionally include a minor vulnerability in the latest patch. This vulnerability will affect random stations within range of this station.</t>
		<t id="100">Your fake identity has been compromised.</t>
		<t id="101">Fake Identity</t>
		<t id="102">Cannot access command menu while station is being hacked.</t>
		<t id="103">Your efforts did not produce any result.</t>
		<t id="104">Frame: %s</t>
		<t id="105">Using private keys to forge secure messages and your fake id to leave a false trail, pin your hacking exploits on your alter ego to further reduce suspicion. This reduces some suspicion</t>
		<t id="106">Approve for Docking</t>
		<t id="107">none</t>
		<t id="108">reduced</t>
		<t id="109">Spoof Sensor Data %s</t>
		<t id="110">Sector Wide: Take Ownership of Stations</t>
		<t id="111">Cannot start this command while \33Y%s\33X is backing hacked.</t>
		<t id="112">Take Ownership of Station</t>
		<t id="113">Station Reactor Overload</t>
		<t id="114">Sector Wide: Station Reactor Overload</t>
		<t id="115">\n(new line)</t>
		<t id="116">Slush Fund</t>
		<t id="117">Steal Ship from Shipyard</t>
		<t id="118">Barter Access for Engine Tunings</t>
		<t id="119">Barter Access for Rudder Optimizations</t>
		<t id="120">Barter Access for Cargobay Shielding</t>
		<t id="121">Success! Your black market contact has marked to delivery point for your goods by placing a navigation satellite for you in sector %s.</t>
		<t id="122">Failure! %s no longer exists.</t>
		<t id="123">%s valued at %scr.</t>
		<t id="124">Bartering...\(\33Y%s\33X%%\)</t>
		<t id="125">Comm Hacking System</t>
	</page>
</language>
